http://www.friendschristian.org/privacy-policy/

Reopening
Search for:
Search
News:   We are open safely for 5 full days/week on campus for grades Preschool-8th. Schedule your tour today! Admissions
BLAST Summer Camp
Calendar
Staff Directory
I am a...
Future Student
Why FCS?
friendschristian.org
I am a...
Future Student
Why FCS?
friendschristian.org
Search:
Search for:
Search
Privacy Policy
Home    /    Privacy Policy
Use of Personal Information
We do not collect any personal information unless you voluntarily provide it by sending us e-mail, participating in a survey, or completing an on-line form. Personal information submitted will not be transferred to any non-affiliated third parties unless otherwise stated at the time of collection. When a user submits personally identifiable information it is used only for the purpose stated at the time of collection.
Consent
Where consent for the use and disclosure of personal information is required, the school will seek consent from the appropriate person. In the case of a student’s personal information, the school will seek the consent from the student and/ or parent depending on the circumstances and the student’s mental ability and maturity to understand the consequences of the proposed use and disclosure.
Cookies
A cookie is a small text file stored by your browser that allows the website to “remember” your preferences such as calendar settings and site bookmarks on the site from visit to visit, or to maintain your “logged in” status when visiting protected areas . Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Web browsers have settings allowing you to reject cookies, or selectively accept cookies, or delete cookies previously accepted. Please be aware that rejecting or deleting cookies from our website may make certain functions unavailable to you.
Log Files
Like most standard website servers we use website statistic packages such as Google Analytics to analyze trends in how our website is accessed and utilized. Information monitored includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, geographic location of visitors (country, city), browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, time spent on pages, and keywords used to find our site via search engines. This information is anonymous and cannot be directly linked to individual users. We may use it to identify high-use or low-use areas of the site, pinpoint problem areas of the site, analyze broad demographic trends in our visitors, and make decisions about how to make it easier for people to find and navigate our website.
Links
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.
Security
This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ personal information. Whenever users submit personal information (such as contact info or credit card info) via online forms, registration, or online purchase, upon submission that information is encrypted via the highest level of SSL (Secured Sockets Layer) available. Servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment. Under no circumstances are credit card numbers permanently stored on our website servers.
Non-secured Communications
Posts to discussion forums, discussion boards, comments to blogs, and Alumni Class Notes are viewable by other users. When these areas are not in a password-protected area, they may be viewable by the general public. Please be aware of this when posting personal information in these areas.
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:admin@friendschristian.org.
Effective as of February 1, 2015
